files32.com 2018-09-05

# Welcome to Files32.com! Free, beta, and shareware software downloads.

Thank you for visiting files32.com. We are committed to protecting the information about our visitors. This privacy policy states how we collect and use the information collected at our site. 

Please note that we do not collect personally identifiable information about our visitors without their consent. The personal information that we have available was submitted to us by the visitors knowingly. This happens in the following cases: 

\- A person is placing an advertisement with our site under his/her personal name  
\- A person is nominating him/herself to be a contact person  
\- A person is sending us an inquiry about our site, services, opportunities to place an ad, etc.

The collection of personal information is stipulated only by the conditions stated above and may include the following data: name, address, telephone and fax numbers, e-mail, business contact details. 

Personal information is used for the creation of our customers’ base, services delivery and information distribution about updates or modifications of our services. The information collected is not used for marketing purposes, neither is it shared, sold or bartered with third parties, nor distributed in any other manner unless it is required by law, governmental or police structures. 

To assure the proper functioning of the site and its services, we at files32.com collect the following technical data from the site visitors: 

\- IP address used to connect a visitor’s computer to the Internet  
\- Browser type and version  
\- Operating system type and version, screen resolution  
\- Date and time of visit  
\- Pages accessed and links followed  
\- Search engine and search keyword use

The collection of the given information helps us to ensure site usability and accessibility. It also allows us to organize our web resource to the utmost convenient degree for users to navigate around the site, download information, and use its resources. We analyze how people are finding our site, what technologies are used to access it and which pages interest them to provide with the smooth and effective service and information. 

We use external advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies will generally store cookies on your computer to record non-personally identifiable information about your visits to find out how you reached the advertiser’s website and the date visited.

We also use Google [Adsense](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) advertising service on our site. Ads provided by Google [Adsense](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) retrieve the information from the website contents not the visitors themselves. Google [Adsense](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of DART cookies enables it to serve ads to the users based on their visit to the current site and to other sites on the Internet. A user may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that files32.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
